[{"answer": "Nicole.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "So what's your name?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "Do you have a question for me?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "New Jersey.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "Do you know?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "By the storm.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "How did your house get broken?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "Have you got new ones?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "You keep going, Nicole.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "Are you directing for me?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "It's incredibly frustrating.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Are you angry that nothing more has been done from this time of period?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "Do you think he will?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "I think that we watch him a lot.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Do you still have confidence in him?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Nicole, do you like being on TV?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "When.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Will you do that for me?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "And some bath toys.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Would you like that?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "You know, it's not, mostly it's been supportive.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "Have you been taken aback by the scale of venom that's come your way?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "I've only got the one hat, and so for what it's worth, I would say all criticism is valid.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "How much of that criticism if you're wearing your Mike Rowe Man of the People hat is valid?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Weddings, funerals.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "And do you still sing opera?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "A burst?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Just when you thought it was safe to go back in Piers' show, the questions begun again, it'll scare the crap out of you.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "Again, just for my benefit, can you do the \"Jaws One\" just when you thought you're safe to get back into the water?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "I'm finished with Ford, I'm finished with \"Dirty Jobs\", really I mean ...", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "So you have just -- you've just finished with Ford, right?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "I'm unemployed for the first time in my adult life.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Are you actually unemployed right now?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "You know, it's odd but I mean seriously it forces you to step back and go, \"OK.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "How does it feel?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "BBM the BlackBerry Messenger.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Did you just say BM?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "You know what that is?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "Actually, I mean I think I do.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "Do you understand how a company can be valued like that when it only employs like under 100 people?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "Simple as that?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "I mean, I would say there's a third observation too which is it's either a willing thing that you do because you believe its good business, or because you're just an altruistic soul, or it's something that you're compelled to do.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "Well, what do you say on this debate?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "Oh man.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "The American dream that I guess helped you become the man you are and the success that you've been, is that dream still obtainable in the same way or has it changed?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "Least regret not having to do again.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "What is the one job you will least regret not having to do again?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "So, there's a thing called a lift pump.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "What was the single worst thing you ever did in the whole lot of series (ph)?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "I'll tell you what, stay here.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "I mean, really, I wouldn't play out?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "I think it's -- any threat of course is serious and this is exacerbated by the fact that we are seeing the spread of al-Qaeda or al-Qaeda \"affiliated organizations.\"", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "What do you know about this and how serious you think it is?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Serious sanctions.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "What is the solution here senator, do you think, to what is clearly a massive problem that's finally erupted in the way that we've seen?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "CCAIN: It's worsening.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "Any improvement there or is it the situation worsening?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "It's just -- it's a free country but that kind of language really doesn't have any place in our political dialog.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "Well, if I were him, because those comments, I would, but because I don't think the people of Texas -- look, I am a severe critic of President Obama particularly on National Security but that kind of language, he's the president of United States, he's been elected and reelected and I believe we should treat him respectfully.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "Should he now distance himself completely from Ted Nugent because of this comment?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "It's a free country.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "What do you make of those comments?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "As a human being, I can't control what they say, how they behave.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "Does it sting?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "You know, I don't know.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "Do you think he could win a nomination by playing that card?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "I believe so.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "Is Chris Christie still a potential serious candidate despite everything has happened?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "But right now, he's sitting home having a parade for himself.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Who are you anyway, Daniel Fruik?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Yes, that's me.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "That's you, right?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "I do now.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "Did you guys know that?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "Well, that's a good question.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "What do you think is being the reason?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Well, it took hundreds of people, four years to make it so it was insanely difficult.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "And Phil, for more logistical and technical point of view, how difficult was it to create animated Lego?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "We never fight.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "Is that hard because normally, there's like one director, right?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Christopher Miller was the huge diva.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "Who the hell was the biggest diva (ph) of all those?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "Gosh.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "I'm doing the red carpet for CNN on Sunday March 2nd, what are you tips -- is it a win best movie do you think?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "Honestly, you know, they're also different but we were talking before about the Wolf of Wall Street.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "What's been the best movie you've seen recently?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "Yeah, yeah.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "It flies by, isn't it?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "Jobless, I think homeless and falling sleep on my desk, pretty ignominious end to one of the great careers on American TV.", "docId": "140220pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "Walmart?", "qSentId": 652}]